Anthony Super

http://anthony.noided.media anthony@noided.media http://github.com/anthonysuper

Bio

A developer with 2.5 years experience, primarily working in backend web development using technologies such as Ruby on Rails and Sinatra. I have extensive experience working with databases and automated testing, as well as with using jQuery and React.js on the front end. I also have experience in Java, as well as in Linux systems administration. Additionally, I have worked with C, C++, Objective-C, and Python.

Work Experience

CEO/LEAD BACKEND DEVELOPER, NOIDED MEDIA LLC - 2014-PRESENT

Founded Noided Media LLC, a web development company. I am its chief backend developer on all of its websites. Its projects include:

- Imagehex, an art sharing website. Ruby on Rails for the backend with Postgres as a database. I
 also wrote quite a bit of React.js for a more satisfying experience on the front end.
- Fiction Dock, a fan fiction website. Ruby on Rails for the backend with Postgres as a database.
- WavHead, a democratic DJ that lets anybody at a party vote on what to play next. Ruby with Sinatra, using SQLite as a DB.

OPEN SOURCE WORK - 2013-PRESENT

I work on a variety of open source projects, both as a contributor and as a maintainer. A list of my projects on can be found on my Github (github.com/anthonysuper).

INDEPENDENT TECHNICAL SUPPORT – 2012-PRESENT

Provide technical support and educational services for OS X and Windows.

OPEN SPACE TECHNICIAN, HRMD, HIGHLANDS RANCH, COLORADO – 2015

Worked as a technician improving and repairing the trails around Highlands Ranch.

BELLA WOMAN'S CARE, VIDEO EDITING, 2014

Volunteered and edited promotional material for a Denver-based woman's nonprofit health clinic.

Achievements

- AP Scholars Aware, 2-Time Recipient
- National Merit Program Letter of Recommendation
- FBLA Neworking Concepts Statewide 2nd Place, 2014
- Code Club Founder/Teacher, ThunderRidge High School

Education

ThunderRidge High School, HS Diploma – 2015

Colorado State University, Bachelors in Computer Science, Freshman Year – Present